{
    "id": "ee1ba12826d04bb590d31a7d73381838",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I told him ................................. be late.",
            "description": "We put not before the infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "to not",
                "not to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2de138a65a614342868c41a933235d13"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked us .................................. our assignments.",
            "description": "Imperatives are reported with a to-infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "that we submit",
                "to submit"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "98a8420e111947dabcfed86ddc857c75"
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked me if I ..................................... her before.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "have seen",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "203916be4fd94ae2b73b40363eb0dbb0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He told us ...................................... on time.",
            "description": "Imperatives are reported with to-infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "that be",
                "to be"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7f1419cd597f4715a4418188cb98c651"
        },
        {
            "question": "He told me ......................................... for him.",
            "description": "Imperatives are reported with to-infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "to wait",
                "wait",
                "waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0a98d77b0cb540c6910f4570315ff284"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked if I ..................................... the answer.",
            "description": "When the main verb is in the past tense, the subordinate verb, too, will most probably be in the past tense. ",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "had known"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "66ebc9699bc94f8f82553c70350c0b63"
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked the manager if I .................................. leave early.",
            "description": "When the main verb is in the past tense, the subordinate verb, too, will most probably be in the past tense. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d95c4183aa2841f5a4d14e4cc300f1f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "They asked me ........................................ interested in the offer.",
            "description": "We use the normal word order in indirect questions - that means the subject goes before the auxiliary. ",
            "answers": [
                "if was I",
                "if I was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d87f2fef91c8408abaa79fe28a7fc118"
        },
        {
            "question": "I told him ........................................ not coming.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that I was",
                "that I am",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ce4358c38874b4193dbf6796bde950b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that no one .......................................... forward to help her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came",
                "had come",
                "has come"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c65e3870bf364d849e3050fff2aede46"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked me what I ...................................... do if I lost my job.",
            "description": "When the main verb is in the past tense, the subordinate verb, too, will most probably be in the past tense. ",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f7181ab1e02b4d6f9cc5c737dcd3f7ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "They encouraged her .................................... another attempt.",
            "description": "Encourage is followed by object + to-infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "make",
                "to make",
                "making"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0edb996c6e694144afe80c2ec0b62500"
        }
    ]
}